<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>songwriting on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/songwriting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in songwriting on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/songwriting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ode To ADF</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</guid>
      <description>A few months back, I penned this satire about Microsoft Azure Data Factory (ADF). It&amp;rsquo;s a mix of my day job as a developer converging with my passion, music and songwriting. Today I decided to take a swing at updating the drums for it.
If you are a software developer who uses ADF, you may find it funny!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name More Beautiful</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was reading Romans and tears came to my eyes as I just got a great sense of how much God loves me and you. His great sacrifice means great hope for this sinner. I wrote this that same day. I hope it encourages you somehow, some way. This song was released March 28, 2025.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh What a Savior (demo)</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the first verse of this a couple of weeks back. I tinkered and toyed with it here and there as time allowed. Finally, this afternoon, I worked on it until it became what you hear in this video. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot On the Grass</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</guid>
      <description>I started working on this song earlier this week. Different guitars inspire different ideas and I found myself enjoying this one on the resonator guitar. I recorded this using my iPhone; I hope you enjoy it! I&amp;rsquo;ll be working in the future to record more than a demo of it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</guid>
      <description>Chasing Rainbows is an upbeat guitar instrumental recorded at home using a Guild mahogany guitar in front of a Shure 57 mic. I shot the photographs in Breckinridge County, Kentucky.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Need You</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</guid>
      <description>Recorded in November 2022, I Need You is a short simple personal confession&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Gonna Change Your World</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</guid>
      <description>Love and support those around you who have dyslexia! Learn more about dyslexia at https://w1.mtsu.edu/dyslexia/.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 07:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I shared this tune with a friend of mine in New Orleans. He told me it was a perfect song for the times.
Perhaps Tomorrow is a song I might give to my younger self given the chance. Life can be hard and doesn’t pull punches. One makes mistakes, but tomorrow is a new day! It’s a chance to heal, to move on, to go a new direction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
