<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/art/</guid>
      <description>Candidly, this page is a work in progress. Below is a really small subset of my watercolor work. The plan is to add more in the coming days and weeks.
At this time, if you care to view many more examples of my watercolor work, as well as my pencil work, be sure to visit my Instagram feed!
   The purpose of art is washing the dust of daily life off our souls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Friends in My Backyard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/books/</guid>
      <description>My first children&amp;rsquo;s book, Looking for Friends in My Backyard is a story I wrote and illustrated with my grandsons in mind. It covers a day in the life of a little boy exploring his own backyard. Come along for the adventure!

Check it out:
Amazon
Books-A-Million
BookPatch LLC
 Pssssst! Want some FREE color sheets related to this book? Check out my post &amp;mdash; posts/colorsheets/.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name More Beautiful</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/thenamemorebeautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/thenamemorebeautiful/</guid>
      <description>After doing some reading in the book of Romans, I got a great sense of how much God loves me and you. His great sacrifice means great hope for this sinner. I wrote this that same day. I hope it encourages you somehow, some way.
 
Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayfaring Stranger</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/wayfaringstranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/wayfaringstranger/</guid>
      <description>Wayfaring Stranger has been covered by so many singers and artists over the years; I heard this tune when I was a young boy. I stumbled across sheet music to it and played around with the idea you hear below. I hope you enjoy my take on this one!
 
Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Lost</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/paradiselost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/paradiselost/</guid>
      <description>Released!!! (October 15, 2024)
Paradise Lost features 7 original instrumental works.
The title track is like a beach&amp;rsquo;s edge creating a line against the unending sea that rolls into the distance, the intro synths of “Paradise Lost” chill and calm. The crank of electric guitar mid way through reflect the Cherubim’s driving humanity into the world that awaits just outside. As the track plays out, there are glimpses of the peaceful creation left behind mixed with a new world of choices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Hours</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/afterhours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/afterhours/</guid>
      <description>I grew up listening to a lot of different musical styles. Living about 60 miles north of New Orleans back then, some late Summer nights and weekends I would try to tune my old radio to those distant Jazz stations. After Hours is an attempt to create something smooth and jazz like. I used a Gretsch Streamliner for both guitar tracks, and a Fernandes bass. I hope you enjoy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Christmas Hymns</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/3christmashymns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/3christmashymns/</guid>
      <description>Recorded in 2017, this project includes three Christmas hymns. One is an instrumental.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1978</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/1978/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/1978/</guid>
      <description>A rock instrumental featuring a 1978 Ibanez Les Paul PF100! I picked up this guitar on the used rack at a local Nashville guitar shop. I fell in love with it&amp;rsquo;s playability and sound.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Simple piano and raspy vocals underpin a soulful ballad about keeping the faith and not giving up on tomorrow!
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</guid>
      <description>Dawn of a New Day is a keyboard / synthesizer based instrumental work with cinematic overtones. Inspired by the thought that the future is still ahead, the past is behind! Seize the dawn of a new day&amp;hellip;
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfinished Business</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</guid>
      <description>Released in 2018, Unfinished Business was a labor of love featuring 7 original piano based works. Tracks that appeared to interest listeners are On Hold, Workin&#39; Toward Something, and Pillow Fight.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Where Fast</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</guid>
      <description>No Where Fast released in March 2018, arrived with 10 original songs! Some of the fan favorites are &amp;hellip;
Pretty Little Lies &amp;ndash; a cynical commentary of the times, Now I Do, a ballad about the blessings of small town life, and Road To Amarillo, a guitar grooving instrumental!
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Way from Home</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</guid>
      <description>Containing 12 original songs and recorded in 2017, Long Way from Home features a mix of songs ranging from warm ballads like Don&amp;rsquo;t Go Away to upbeat Goin&#39; Down This Road. Thought provoking lyrical tracks like Things to Think About remind one of what is important at the end of the day! There is an underlying feel to much of this recording that is Eagle&amp;rsquo;s like.
 Also find it here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ode To ADF</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</guid>
      <description>A few months back, I penned this satire about Microsoft Azure Data Factory (ADF). It&amp;rsquo;s a mix of my day job as a developer converging with my passion, music and songwriting. Today I decided to take a swing at updating the drums for it.
If you are a software developer who uses ADF, you may find it funny!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name More Beautiful</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was reading Romans and tears came to my eyes as I just got a great sense of how much God loves me and you. His great sacrifice means great hope for this sinner. I wrote this that same day. I hope it encourages you somehow, some way. This song was released March 28, 2025.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/saying-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/saying-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Sadly this past March we said goodbye to a part of our family, Lucas. Lucas came into our lives a little over nine years ago. We knew he was getting older, but when he slowed down a good bit during his daily walks, we didn&amp;rsquo;t quite realize there was something more going on.
My wife took him for his regular nail clipping and the veterinarian noticed he wasn&amp;rsquo;t himself. She asked to do some scans and the resulting news rattled our world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayfaring Stranger</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/wayfaring-stranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/wayfaring-stranger/</guid>
      <description>Using a Gretsch resonator guitar for both the rhythm and lead parts, here is my take on Wayfaring Stranger. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/happy-new-year-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/happy-new-year-2025/</guid>
      <description>Dear Reader, Happy New Year to you and your family! 2024 is gone now forever.
It seems as one grows older that the years pick up speed and that our days are truly but a vapor. Reading Psalm 39:5 (NKJV), Indeed, You have made my days as handbreadths, And my age is as nothing before You; Certainly every man at his best state is but vapor. Selah
Typically, for me, today is a day of reflection on past goals, and where I am in relation to those goals, both in the near term and in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvisation 001 -- Gibson J-45 Standard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/improv-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/improv-001/</guid>
      <description>This gentle guitar improvisation was a test drive of the Gibson J-45 Standard. The recording was made with the guitar plugged directly without external mics. In these turbulent times I hope you find the music calming and peaceful.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Lost</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/paradise-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 01:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/paradise-lost/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I laid down the synth sounds to this track using a Fishman TriplePlay Connect attached to a Stratocaster. This was really a lot of fun. I added the lead guitar track a couple of weeks later using one of the selections from a Fender Mustang LT-25. The cover pic was simply shot using an iPhone with the Classic Hipstamatic app with my own config for black and white frames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Work In Progress (May 2024)</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-work-in-progress-may-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-work-in-progress-may-2024/</guid>
      <description>This is a little piece I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on; I think it sounds peaceful and balanced on the Martin 000-15SM, a mahogany acoustic guitar. I picked this up used at https://www.rumbleseatmusic.com in Nashville.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also been tinkering with a slide and different tunings on this guitar. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll share some of that in future videos.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh What a Savior (demo)</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the first verse of this a couple of weeks back. I tinkered and toyed with it here and there as time allowed. Finally, this afternoon, I worked on it until it became what you hear in this video. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot On the Grass</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</guid>
      <description>I started working on this song earlier this week. Different guitars inspire different ideas and I found myself enjoying this one on the resonator guitar. I recorded this using my iPhone; I hope you enjoy it! I&amp;rsquo;ll be working in the future to record more than a demo of it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</guid>
      <description>This is a small test drive of a Gretsch 9220 Resonator guitar with all mahogany body. Though it has a mic pickup, I mic&amp;rsquo;d it with a Shure SM-57. I am no sound engineer, but I felt like this simple recording came out nicely.
I hope you enjoy this short demo.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</guid>
      <description>Chasing Rainbows is an upbeat guitar instrumental recorded at home using a Guild mahogany guitar in front of a Shure 57 mic. I shot the photographs in Breckinridge County, Kentucky.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Need You</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</guid>
      <description>Recorded in November 2022, I Need You is a short simple personal confession&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Gonna Change Your World</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</guid>
      <description>Love and support those around you who have dyslexia! Learn more about dyslexia at https://w1.mtsu.edu/dyslexia/.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until The Last Heartbeat</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 15:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</guid>
      <description>This guitar instrumental was recorded at my home. The rhythm guitar used was a Taylor 110e and the lead guitar used was an Epiphone PR5E/N Nylon stringed guitar. I used a Fernandez bass for the bass track.
I dedicate this to my wife. I will continue to love you and cherish you until the last heartbeat&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Melody</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas!!! I was scheduled to share the following arrangement this morning at church. I woke up with the sinus crud and won&amp;rsquo;t be there. This was recorded earlier in the week during a practice session.
I pray your Christmas is filled with the love of family and friends. Whether you have sweet memories from the past, or not, may there be time now to make new memories with those around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Music Coming</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/new-music-12-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/new-music-12-2023/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to say that soon you can purchase, and stream, a couple of new guitar instrumentals. Lend an ear and take the new tunes for a spin on your favorite service.
I know they are very different styles! What can I say? I love playing and experimenting.
I hope you enjoy them as much as I did making playing and recording them.

December 4 -- 1978 will be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Summer Thrill</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/last-summer-thrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/last-summer-thrill/</guid>
      <description>This is a guitar instrumental demo recorded at home using a Gretsch Streamliner in Logic Pro X. This recording is comprised of 3 tracks: drums via the Logic Pro X drummer, a Fernandes bass track I played, and finally the Gretsch Streamliner. I hope you like it!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Calls</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/autumn-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/autumn-calls/</guid>
      <description>A slight chill eases into the evening air. Leaves drift sharing their color all around while evenings fill with the crackling of old wood in the fire-pit. This short acoustic guitar track was something I noodled today that made me think of Autumn. Lucas our Labrador makes his first music debut in the early seconds of the track. I hope you like. 😀
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1978</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/1978/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/1978/</guid>
      <description>This is a guitar demo using a 1978 Ibanez PF100 (shown in the photo) plugged into a Korg G3 processor. I had fun laying down the bass and guitar tracks. I hope you like!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software I Use</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/software-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 06:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/software-i-use/</guid>
      <description>In an era not so far away I once purchased and used expensive software to edit images and build web site animations. I am looking at you Adobe Photoshop and Macromedia Flash. I bought updates over the years excited to get some new feature that promised to wow my customers and make my life easier and building output faster.
I was hooked until the subscription service model became the standard. I didn&amp;rsquo;t like buying use of something I would technically never own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Got This (demo).</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/you-got-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/you-got-this/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it seems we are given more challenges in life than others. We often wonder why? Somedays I think we need to be encouraged to keep on keeping on.
 Don&amp;rsquo;t you give up!  Don&amp;rsquo;t surrender!  You&amp;rsquo;re a fighter, a strong contender!  You got this!  You&amp;rsquo;re gonna overcome!!! 
I wrote this for my friend Matt who now lives in Indiana! You got this! You&amp;rsquo;re gonna overcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Done with You.</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/done-with-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/done-with-you/</guid>
      <description>A while back I heard someone use the phrase “I’m done with you” in a playful sense. Recorded at home without a lot of dazzle, here’s my take on that phrase.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/kentucky-landscapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/kentucky-landscapes/</guid>
      <description>&#34;
Recently my wife and I drove to Northwestern Kentucky to help our son-in-law and youngest daughter get unpacked and settled into their new home. Between some of the unboxing and furniture moving I captured these frames using my little iPhone (SE2 model). Though I think these frames are nice, I wish I had taken my Nikon D-70 to see what I could have captured with it.
&#34;
&#34;
Over the span of a few days we experienced heavy afternoon rains, some large sized hail, and saw some beautiful clouds driven by fervent winds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martha Jane.</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/martha-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/martha-jane/</guid>
      <description>Over the years in our home I made up silly songs about various subjects. One day a few years ago, I started calling my wife Martha Jane teasingly. The little rhyme — &amp;ldquo;Martha Jane, dancin’ in the pourin’ rain&amp;rdquo; came into being.
This silly song makes me smile. I hope you enjoy it too!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas 2022</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/merry-christmas-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/merry-christmas-2022/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas &amp;amp; all the best to you and your family! It has been quite an interesting year.
While I have largely been silent here on the blog, and on social media, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy on a number of fronts. I plan to share more in the new year. For now enjoy your time with those around you.
Wayne
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Random Photo Works</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/some-random-photo-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/some-random-photo-works/</guid>
      <description>The last time I checked I had more than 40,000 frames stored that I had taken using my Nikon D70. I have been occasionally going through them and sharing them on my Facebook and Instagram accounts. As you can see below I really have a thing for landscapes! 😀 There are some other subjects in the mix too.

Above: Over The Hill, taken in Gatlinburg, Tennessee on a weekend trip with my wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep the Wonder</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/keep-the-wonder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/keep-the-wonder/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes we find that one thing that ignites our being and fuels our creativity. I was 16 when my mom gave me the gift that would be a direction setter for the rest of my life. It was a Ricoh KR-5 Super 35mm single lens reflex camera. I used it through high school snapping frames for the yearbook and newspaper. I would go on to learn how to process black and white Kodak film using D50 chemicals, which by the way, landed me a high school job at my small town&amp;rsquo;s local newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/catching-up/</guid>
      <description>The cold wind stirs and the sleeting rain pours just outside my window. I long for spring temperatures and more sunlight. Some prep work has been done around the house and yard in faith that the 2022 garden season will bear a fresh beautiful batch of vegetables. My wife and I enjoy our time together working in our garden.
Since I posted my &amp;lsquo;Something New, Something Old&amp;rsquo; post back in November 2021, I have been continuing on my trek learning Elixir, and functional programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>As we slow down to celebrate Christmas with our families, friends, and coworkers, I want to say thank you to all of you who purchased a song or two, streamed my music, or purchased a copy of my children&amp;rsquo;s book this year!
I pray your Christmas is filled with peace, joy, and love, and that the new year will bring you hope and anticipation of new friendships, new directions, and a rekindled zest for life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something New, Something Old</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/something-new-something-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 05:53:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/something-new-something-old/</guid>
      <description>Working with technology in my day job, I enjoy reading various sources and learning what others are doing with technologies they use in their day jobs and lives. Two sites that I frequent are Hacker News and Slashdot.org.
On Hacker News I have noticed links about a technology called Elixir. Candidly, I skipped over them because there are so many technologies available these days, and only so many hours a day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercolor for a Coworker</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 11:18:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</guid>
      <description>&#34;
I have been well known to doodle, cartoon, caricature, and sketch coworkers through the last few years. At one employer, it was a regular thing having new hires brought by my cubicle entry for me to take a photo of them and draw them later.😃
I think some times we have jobs where it meets the need of earning a check, providing insurance coverage, and not much else. If we are blessed, we may find those positions where we feel good about what we are doing daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Empty Sketchbook</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</guid>
      <description>Last Christmas (2020) my wife gave me a nice sketchbook. I was excited by it. I could imagine it filled with all kinds of interesting sketches, some watercolor ideas, and generally filled with cool art.
Here I am in late September 2021, and well, the sketchbook&amp;rsquo;s pages have remained free of pencil marks, watercolors, or ideas from yours truly.
Admittedly this year I have not cranked out as many new pieces of art as in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Free Colorsheets</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/colorsheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/colorsheets/</guid>
      <description>You can download the following items for FREE! You don&amp;rsquo;t have to purchase my book, Looking For Friends In My Backyard, in order to enjoy some colorsheets. I created these based on the artwork from the book. Simply click the image of the sheet, or sheets, you wish to download and print. Enjoy!!!
Note: When you click one of the images to download, it will open in a new tab!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 07:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I shared this tune with a friend of mine in New Orleans. He told me it was a perfect song for the times.
Perhaps Tomorrow is a song I might give to my younger self given the chance. Life can be hard and doesn’t pull punches. One makes mistakes, but tomorrow is a new day! It’s a chance to heal, to move on, to go a new direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking For Friends In My Backyard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/lookingforfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 17:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/lookingforfriends/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to share that I have a new children&amp;rsquo;s book &amp;ndash; Looking For Friends In My Backyard.
Looking For Friends In My Backyard is about a day in the life of a little boy exploring his backyard! The illustrations are watercolor pieces that I did myself.

You can order your copy today on Amazon.com!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midiman driver for Mac OS Catalina and Big Sur</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/midimanonmacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 07:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/midimanonmacos/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a little Midiman 1x1 Sport that I love using. It uses phantom power and is small enough to haul around if needed. I have other gear that I can use to replace it, but I wanted to keep using this device.
The Midiman 1x1 Sport does NOT work with Mac OS Catalina, or Big Sur without a 64 bit driver update. There is NO updated driver from the manufacturer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slowin&#39; Down</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to be slowing down much of the time so that I could enjoy the little things in life. Like so many of us, I find myself pulled in a number of directions trying to keep it all moving in the right direction. I&amp;rsquo;d like to practice what I preach, but in honesty, the only slowing down I might do today would be to share this track!
This is a simple instrumental with a little vocal harmony near the end; I recorded it at home using Logic Pro X, a Focusrite 18i8, a tele custom, and a Shure SM58; I hope you like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Begins</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/itbegins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 18:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/itbegins/</guid>
      <description>Last year when Covid hit and most of us found ourselves working at home, my wife, a school teacher, and I started a garden. It became one of the things that we both found ourselves looking forward to daily. Now a year later, we have begun our planning for this year&amp;rsquo;s garden!
The excitement and anticipation of the Cater Garden 2021, is upon us! We look forward to Spring and the days ahead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Conversation</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/sweetconversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 18:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/sweetconversation/</guid>
      <description>I recently sat down here at home and recorded this calming jazz piano piece. I hope you like it!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrations In Progress</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/illustrationsinprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 20:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/illustrationsinprogress/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote a little poem from the perspective of my youngest grandson. My family and some friends fell in love with the story.
I started sketching and watercoloring the illustrations for it. After working through a number of the illustrations, I shared electronic copies of the work with a few folks. The illustrations were well received, but I wanted to do a little better. The holidays came, and I got busy with my day job, so I put the illustration work on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Billy Wayne Cater. My friends call me Wayne!
I am a songwriter, but isn’t everyone in Nashville? I play guitar and tinker with other instruments &amp;ndash; piano / keyboard, and bass guitar. I am an ASCAP member. You can find my music work on Apple Music, Amazon Music, Spotify, and your favorite music service.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a day job too! I’ve been a software developer for 25+ years. These days I spend my time using C#.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
