<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/art/</guid>
      <description>Candidly, this page is a work in progress. Below is a really small subset of my watercolor work. The plan is to add more in the coming days and weeks.
At this time, if you care to view many more examples of my watercolor work, as well as my pencil work, be sure to visit my Instagram feed!
   The purpose of art is washing the dust of daily life off our souls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Friends in My Backyard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/books/</guid>
      <description>My first children&amp;rsquo;s book, Looking for Friends in My Backyard is a story I wrote and illustrated with my grandsons in mind. It covers a day in the life of a little boy exploring his own backyard. Come along for the adventure!

Check it out:
Amazon
Barnes &amp;amp; Noble
Books-A-Million
BookPatch LLC
Walmart
 PSSSST!!! You can download FREE colorsheets generated from some of the artwork in the book! Visit my post &amp;ndash; colorsheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Simple piano and raspy vocals underpin a soulful ballad about keeping the faith and not giving up on tomorrow!

Check it out:
Apple Music
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</guid>
      <description>Dawn of a New Day is a keyboard / synthesizer based instrumental work with cinematic overtones. Inspired by the thought that the future is still ahead, the past is behind! Seize the dawn of a new day&amp;hellip;

Check it out:
Apple Music
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfinished Business</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</guid>
      <description>Released in September 2018, Unfinished Business was a labor of love featuring 7 original piano based works. Tracks that appeared to interest listeners were On Hold, Workin&#39; Toward Something, and Pillow Fight.

Check it out:
Apple Music
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Where Fast</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</guid>
      <description>No Where Fast released in March 2018, arrived with 10 original songs! Some of the fan favorites are &amp;hellip;
Pretty Little Lies &amp;ndash; a cynical commentary of the times, Now I Do, a ballad about the blessings of small town life, and Road To Amarillo, a guitar grooving instrumental!

Check it out:
Apple Music
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Way from Home</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</guid>
      <description>Containing 12 original songs and recorded in 2017, Long Way from Home features a mix of songs ranging from warm ballads like Don&amp;rsquo;t Go Away to upbeat Goin&#39; Down This Road. Thought provoking lyrical tracks like Things to Think About remind one of what is important at the end of the day! There is an underlying feel to much of this recording that is Eagle&amp;rsquo;s like.

Check it out:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>As we slow down to celebrate Christmas with our families, friends, and coworkers, I want to say thank you to all of you who purchased a song or two, streamed my music, or purchased a copy of my children&amp;rsquo;s book this year!
I pray your Christmas is filled with peace, joy, and love, and that the new year will bring you hope and anticipation of new friendships, new directions, and a rekindled zest for life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something New, Something Old</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/something-new-something-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 05:53:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/something-new-something-old/</guid>
      <description>Working with technology in my day job, I enjoy reading various sources and learning what others are doing with technologies they use in their day jobs and lives. Two sites that I frequent are Hacker News and Slashdot.org.
On Hacker News I have noticed links about a technology called Elixir. Candidly, I skipped over them because there are so many technologies available these days, and only so many hours a day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercolor for a Coworker</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 11:18:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</guid>
      <description>&#34;
I have been well known to doodle, cartoon, caricature, and sketch coworkers through the last few years. At one employer, it was a regular thing having new hires brought by my cubicle entry for me to take a photo of them and draw them later.😃
I think some times we have jobs where it meets the need of earning a check, providing insurance coverage, and not much else. If we are blessed, we may find those positions where we feel good about what we are doing daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Empty Sketchbook</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</guid>
      <description>Last Christmas (2020) my wife gave me a nice sketchbook. I was excited by it. I could imagine it filled with all kinds of interesting sketches, some watercolor ideas, and generally filled with cool art.
Here I am in late September 2021, and well, the sketchbook&amp;rsquo;s pages have remained free of pencil marks, watercolors, or ideas from yours truly.
Admittedly this year I have not cranked out as many new pieces of art as in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Free Colorsheets</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/colorsheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/colorsheets/</guid>
      <description>You can download the following items for FREE! You don&amp;rsquo;t have to purchase my book, Looking For Friends In My Backyard, in order to enjoy some colorsheets. I created these based on the artwork from the book. Simply click the image of the sheet, or sheets, you wish to download and print. Enjoy!!!
Note: When you click one of the images to download, it will open in a new tab!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 07:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I shared this tune with a friend of mine in New Orleans. He told me it was a perfect song for the times.
Perhaps Tomorrow is a song I might give to my younger self given the chance. Life can be hard and doesn’t pull punches. One makes mistakes, but tomorrow is a new day! It’s a chance to heal, to move on, to go a new direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking For Friends In My Backyard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/lookingforfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 17:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/lookingforfriends/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to share that I have a new children&amp;rsquo;s book &amp;ndash; Looking For Friends In My Backyard.
Looking For Friends In My Backyard is about a day in the life of a little boy exploring his backyard! The illustrations are watercolor pieces that I did myself.

You can order your copy today on Amazon.com!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midiman driver for Mac OS Catalina and Big Sur</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/midimanonmacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 07:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/midimanonmacos/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a little Midiman 1x1 Sport that I love using. It uses phantom power and is small enough to haul around if needed. I have other gear that I can use to replace it, but I wanted to keep using this device.
The Midiman 1x1 Sport does NOT work with Mac OS Catalina, or Big Sur without a 64 bit driver update. There is NO updated driver from the manufacturer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing the Wind</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasingthewind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasingthewind/</guid>
      <description>A little something from 2 years back&amp;hellip;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slowin&#39; Down</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to be slowing down much of the time so that I could enjoy the little things in life. Like so many of us, I find myself pulled in a number of directions trying to keep it all moving in the right direction. I&amp;rsquo;d like to practice what I preach, but in honesty, the only slowing down I might do today would be to share this track!
This is a simple instrumental with a little vocal harmony near the end; I recorded it at home using Logic Pro X, a Focusrite 18i8, a tele custom, and a Shure SM58; I hope you like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Begins</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/itbegins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 18:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/itbegins/</guid>
      <description>Last year when Covid hit and most of us found ourselves working at home, my wife, a school teacher, and I started a garden. It became one of the things that we both found ourselves looking forward to daily. Now a year later, we have begun our planning for this year&amp;rsquo;s garden!
The excitement and anticipation of the Cater Garden 2021, is upon us! We look forward to Spring and the days ahead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Conversation</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/sweetconversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 18:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/sweetconversation/</guid>
      <description>I recently sat down here at home and recorded this calming jazz piano piece. I hope you like it!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illustrations In Progress</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/illustrationsinprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 20:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/illustrationsinprogress/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote a little poem from the perspective of my youngest grandson. My family and some friends fell in love with the story.
I started sketching and watercoloring the illustrations for it. After working through a number of the illustrations, I shared electronic copies of the work with a few folks. The illustrations were well received, but I wanted to do a little better. The holidays came, and I got busy with my day job, so I put the illustration work on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Billy Wayne Cater. My friends call me Wayne!
I am a songwriter, but isn’t everyone in Nashville? I play guitar and tinker with other instruments &amp;ndash; piano / keyboard, and bass guitar. I am an ASCAP member. You can find some of my music work on Apple Music, Amazon Music, Spotify, and others.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a day job too! I’ve been a software developer for 25 years. The technologies I use these days are C#.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
