<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 09:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Melody</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas!!! I was scheduled to share the following arrangement this morning at church. I woke up with the sinus crud and won&amp;rsquo;t be there. This was recorded earlier in the week during a practice session.
I pray your Christmas is filled with the love of family and friends. Whether you have sweet memories from the past, or not, may there be time now to make new memories with those around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas 2022</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/merry-christmas-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/merry-christmas-2022/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas &amp;amp; all the best to you and your family! It has been quite an interesting year.
While I have largely been silent here on the blog, and on social media, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy on a number of fronts. I plan to share more in the new year. For now enjoy your time with those around you.
Wayne
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>As we slow down to celebrate Christmas with our families, friends, and coworkers, I want to say thank you to all of you who purchased a song or two, streamed my music, or purchased a copy of my children&amp;rsquo;s book this year!
I pray your Christmas is filled with peace, joy, and love, and that the new year will bring you hope and anticipation of new friendships, new directions, and a rekindled zest for life!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
