<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>art on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in art on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Keep the Wonder</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/keep-the-wonder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/keep-the-wonder/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes we find that one thing that ignites our being and fuels our creativity. I was 16 when my mom gave me the gift that would be a direction setter for the rest of my life. It was a Ricoh KR-5 Super 35mm single lens reflex camera. I used it through high school snapping frames for the yearbook and newspaper. I would go on to learn how to process black and white Kodak film using D50 chemicals, which by the way, landed me a high school job at my small town&amp;rsquo;s local newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercolor for a Coworker</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 11:18:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/watercolor-for-a-coworker/</guid>
      <description>&#34;
I have been well known to doodle, cartoon, caricature, and sketch coworkers through the last few years. At one employer, it was a regular thing having new hires brought by my cubicle entry for me to take a photo of them and draw them later.😃
I think some times we have jobs where it meets the need of earning a check, providing insurance coverage, and not much else. If we are blessed, we may find those positions where we feel good about what we are doing daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Empty Sketchbook</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/theemptysketchbook/</guid>
      <description>Last Christmas (2020) my wife gave me a nice sketchbook. I was excited by it. I could imagine it filled with all kinds of interesting sketches, some watercolor ideas, and generally filled with cool art.
Here I am in late September 2021, and well, the sketchbook&amp;rsquo;s pages have remained free of pencil marks, watercolors, or ideas from yours truly.
Admittedly this year I have not cranked out as many new pieces of art as in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
