<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2024 on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2024 on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 09:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Improvisation 001 -- Gibson J-45 Standard</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/improv-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/improv-001/</guid>
      <description>This gentle guitar improvisation was a test drive of the Gibson J-45 Standard. The recording was made with the guitar plugged directly without external mics. In these turbulent times I hope you find the music calming and peaceful.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Lost</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/paradise-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 01:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/paradise-lost/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I laid down the synth sounds to this track using a Fishman TriplePlay Connect attached to a Stratocaster. This was really a lot of fun. I added the lead guitar track a couple of weeks later using one of the selections from a Fender Mustang LT-25. The cover pic was simply shot using an iPhone with the Classic Hipstamatic app with my own config for black and white frames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Work In Progress (May 2024)</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-work-in-progress-may-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-work-in-progress-may-2024/</guid>
      <description>This is a little piece I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on; I think it sounds peaceful and balanced on the Martin 000-15SM, a mahogany acoustic guitar. I picked this up used at https://www.rumbleseatmusic.com in Nashville.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also been tinkering with a slide and different tunings on this guitar. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll share some of that in future videos.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh What a Savior (demo)</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the first verse of this a couple of weeks back. I tinkered and toyed with it here and there as time allowed. Finally, this afternoon, I worked on it until it became what you hear in this video. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot On the Grass</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</guid>
      <description>I started working on this song earlier this week. Different guitars inspire different ideas and I found myself enjoying this one on the resonator guitar. I recorded this using my iPhone; I hope you enjoy it! I&amp;rsquo;ll be working in the future to record more than a demo of it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</guid>
      <description>This is a small test drive of a Gretsch 9220 Resonator guitar with all mahogany body. Though it has a mic pickup, I mic&amp;rsquo;d it with a Shure SM-57. I am no sound engineer, but I felt like this simple recording came out nicely.
I hope you enjoy this short demo.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</guid>
      <description>Chasing Rainbows is an upbeat guitar instrumental recorded at home using a Guild mahogany guitar in front of a Shure 57 mic. I shot the photographs in Breckinridge County, Kentucky.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Gonna Change Your World</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</guid>
      <description>Love and support those around you who have dyslexia! Learn more about dyslexia at https://w1.mtsu.edu/dyslexia/.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until The Last Heartbeat</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 15:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</guid>
      <description>This guitar instrumental was recorded at my home. The rhythm guitar used was a Taylor 110e and the lead guitar used was an Epiphone PR5E/N Nylon stringed guitar. I used a Fernandez bass for the bass track.
I dedicate this to my wife. I will continue to love you and cherish you until the last heartbeat&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
