<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>guitar on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/guitar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in guitar on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/guitar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot On the Grass</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/barefoot-on-the-grass/</guid>
      <description>I started working on this song earlier this week. Different guitars inspire different ideas and I found myself enjoying this one on the resonator guitar. I recorded this using my iPhone; I hope you enjoy it! I&amp;rsquo;ll be working in the future to record more than a demo of it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/gretsch-demo/</guid>
      <description>This is a small test drive of a Gretsch 9220 Resonator guitar with all mahogany body. Though it has a mic pickup, I mic&amp;rsquo;d it with a Shure SM-57. I am no sound engineer, but I felt like this simple recording came out nicely.
I hope you enjoy this short demo.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Rainbows</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasing-rainbows/</guid>
      <description>Chasing Rainbows is an upbeat guitar instrumental recorded at home using a Guild mahogany guitar in front of a Shure 57 mic. I shot the photographs in Breckinridge County, Kentucky.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Need You</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/i-need-you/</guid>
      <description>Recorded in November 2022, I Need You is a short simple personal confession&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Gonna Change Your World</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/youre-gonna-change-your-world/</guid>
      <description>Love and support those around you who have dyslexia! Learn more about dyslexia at https://w1.mtsu.edu/dyslexia/.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Until The Last Heartbeat</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 15:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/until-the-last-heartbeat/</guid>
      <description>This guitar instrumental was recorded at my home. The rhythm guitar used was a Taylor 110e and the lead guitar used was an Epiphone PR5E/N Nylon stringed guitar. I used a Fernandez bass for the bass track.
I dedicate this to my wife. I will continue to love you and cherish you until the last heartbeat&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Melody</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/christmas-melody/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas!!! I was scheduled to share the following arrangement this morning at church. I woke up with the sinus crud and won&amp;rsquo;t be there. This was recorded earlier in the week during a practice session.
I pray your Christmas is filled with the love of family and friends. Whether you have sweet memories from the past, or not, may there be time now to make new memories with those around you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Music Coming</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/new-music-12-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/new-music-12-2023/</guid>
      <description>I am excited to say that soon you can purchase, and stream, a couple of new guitar instrumentals. Lend an ear and take the new tunes for a spin on your favorite service.
I know they are very different styles! What can I say? I love playing and experimenting.
I hope you enjoy them as much as I did making playing and recording them.

December 4 -- 1978 will be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Summer Thrill</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/last-summer-thrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/last-summer-thrill/</guid>
      <description>This is a guitar instrumental demo recorded at home using a Gretsch Streamliner in Logic Pro X. This recording is comprised of 3 tracks: drums via the Logic Pro X drummer, a Fernandes bass track I played, and finally the Gretsch Streamliner. I hope you like it!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn Calls</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/autumn-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/autumn-calls/</guid>
      <description>A slight chill eases into the evening air. Leaves drift sharing their color all around while evenings fill with the crackling of old wood in the fire-pit. This short acoustic guitar track was something I noodled today that made me think of Autumn. Lucas our Labrador makes his first music debut in the early seconds of the track. I hope you like. 😀
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1978</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/1978/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/1978/</guid>
      <description>This is a guitar demo using a 1978 Ibanez PF100 (shown in the photo) plugged into a Korg G3 processor. I had fun laying down the bass and guitar tracks. I hope you like!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Got This (demo).</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/you-got-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/you-got-this/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it seems we are given more challenges in life than others. We often wonder why? Somedays I think we need to be encouraged to keep on keeping on.
 Don&amp;rsquo;t you give up!  Don&amp;rsquo;t surrender!  You&amp;rsquo;re a fighter, a strong contender!  You got this!  You&amp;rsquo;re gonna overcome!!! 
I wrote this for my friend Matt who now lives in Indiana! You got this! You&amp;rsquo;re gonna overcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Done with You.</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/done-with-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/done-with-you/</guid>
      <description>A while back I heard someone use the phrase “I’m done with you” in a playful sense. Recorded at home without a lot of dazzle, here’s my take on that phrase.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martha Jane.</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/martha-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/martha-jane/</guid>
      <description>Over the years in our home I made up silly songs about various subjects. One day a few years ago, I started calling my wife Martha Jane teasingly. The little rhyme — &amp;ldquo;Martha Jane, dancin’ in the pourin’ rain&amp;rdquo; came into being.
This silly song makes me smile. I hope you enjoy it too!!!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing the Wind</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasingthewind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/chasingthewind/</guid>
      <description>A little something from 2 years back&amp;hellip;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slowin&#39; Down</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/slowindown/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to be slowing down much of the time so that I could enjoy the little things in life. Like so many of us, I find myself pulled in a number of directions trying to keep it all moving in the right direction. I&amp;rsquo;d like to practice what I preach, but in honesty, the only slowing down I might do today would be to share this track!
This is a simple instrumental with a little vocal harmony near the end; I recorded it at home using Logic Pro X, a Focusrite 18i8, a tele custom, and a Shure SM58; I hope you like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh What a Savior</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/oh-what-a-savior/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the first verse of this a couple of weeks back. I tinkered and toyed with it here and there as time allowed. Finally, this afternoon, I worked on it until it became what you hear in this video. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
