<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2025 on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/tags/2025/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2025 on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/tags/2025/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ode To ADF</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 07:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/ode-to-adf/</guid>
      <description>A few months back, I penned this satire about Microsoft Azure Data Factory (ADF). It&amp;rsquo;s a mix of my day job as a developer converging with my passion, music and songwriting. Today I decided to take a swing at updating the drums for it.
If you are a software developer who uses ADF, you may find it funny!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name More Beautiful</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/the-name-more-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was reading Romans and tears came to my eyes as I just got a great sense of how much God loves me and you. His great sacrifice means great hope for this sinner. I wrote this that same day. I hope it encourages you somehow, some way. This song was released March 28, 2025.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/saying-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/saying-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>Sadly this past March we said goodbye to a part of our family, Lucas. Lucas came into our lives a little over nine years ago. We knew he was getting older, but when he slowed down a good bit during his daily walks, we didn&amp;rsquo;t quite realize there was something more going on.
My wife took him for his regular nail clipping and the veterinarian noticed he wasn&amp;rsquo;t himself. She asked to do some scans and the resulting news rattled our world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayfaring Stranger</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/wayfaring-stranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/wayfaring-stranger/</guid>
      <description>Using a Gretsch resonator guitar for both the rhythm and lead parts, here is my take on Wayfaring Stranger. I hope you like it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/happy-new-year-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/happy-new-year-2025/</guid>
      <description>Dear Reader, Happy New Year to you and your family! 2024 is gone now forever.
It seems as one grows older that the years pick up speed and that our days are truly but a vapor. Reading Psalm 39:5 (NKJV), Indeed, You have made my days as handbreadths, And my age is as nothing before You; Certainly every man at his best state is but vapor. Selah
Typically, for me, today is a day of reflection on past goals, and where I am in relation to those goals, both in the near term and in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
