<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Task List - Ionic based PWA</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/ionic-app-pwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/ionic-app-pwa/</guid>
      <description>Turning the Task List application into a progressive web app or PWA, was not hard at all! If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, or need some guidance about how to do so, be sure to checkout the Ionic documentation.
After building the PWA code base, I had to modify the
 &amp;lt;base href /&amp;gt;
 in the index.html file. I also had to modify paths in the manifest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Ionic</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/ionic-app-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/ionic-app-dev/</guid>
      <description>In my day job I write web applications using Angular and .Net that run on Azure. Since I work in Angular by day it is a pretty easy jump to tinker using it in mobile development.
In my spare time I was playing around with NativeScript using Angular. One day at the office a coworker challenged me to consider Ionic using Angular. I told him I had read about Ionic a few years back, but the comments of slowness on a device kept me from considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Game Engine</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-game-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-game-engine/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago I stumbled across a cool game engine named PixiJS! I downloaded it and created a satirical version of the old Atari game, Kaboom! In my version the &amp;ldquo;bomber&amp;rdquo; was a cartooned version of the CIO of the company I was working for at the time. He was dropping coins from the top that were being caught by the arms of employees. It was made to just to poke fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Photography</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/some-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/some-photography/</guid>
      <description>Sitting here in my easy chair looking over the new Hugo based site, I was thinking about adding a page, or section, to show some of my photography. Over the years I have photographed brides &amp;amp; grooms, family portraits, product lines for companies, music recording sessions at Nashville studios for music artists, farm landscapes, and many other subjects!
 Above: Montgomery Bell State Park, Dickson, Tennessee at sunset; shot on an iphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pleasant Surprise</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/pleasant-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/pleasant-surprise/</guid>
      <description>Today as I added some art to the site, I realized that in 2016 I posted more art per month. I was surprised to see in the years that followed I posted less. While I have posted less in the last few years since, I&amp;rsquo;ve not given up the desire, nor the pencil, or brush!
When I walk the dog, or work in the garden, I stare at the trees, the land, the sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About One&#39;s Self</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/about-ones-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/about-ones-self/</guid>
      <description>While working to flesh out the content for the new site, I find myself hanging on little details. I really don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy writing and talking about myself. I find that I go into editorial mode and overwork the details of &amp;lsquo;what to keep / what to delete&amp;rsquo;.
There are so many little things I could tell you about myself. The little marketing voices start kicking in and they drown out the earthy realism of what could be captured and shared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Start</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-new-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/posts/a-new-start/</guid>
      <description>After the long silence, today is a new start. This site and blog is now being generated using Hugo. If you want an easy to use web site engine that uses markdown syntax and offers some beautiful themes, you should check out Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>