<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recordings on Wayne Cater</title>
    <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recordings on Wayne Cater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://waynecater.com/recordings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wayfaring Stranger</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/wayfaringstranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/wayfaringstranger/</guid>
      <description>Wayfaring Stranger has been covered by so many singers and artists over the years; I heard this tune when I was a young boy. I stumbled across sheet music to it and played around with the idea you hear below. I hope you enjoy my take on this one!
 
Also find it here:
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Lost</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/paradiselost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/paradiselost/</guid>
      <description>Newly Released!!! (October 15, 2024)
Paradise Lost features 7 original instrumental works.
The title track is like a beach&amp;rsquo;s edge creating a line against the unending sea that rolls into the distance, the intro synths of “Paradise Lost” chill and calm. The crank of electric guitar mid way through reflect the Cherubim’s driving humanity into the world that awaits just outside. As the track plays out, there are glimpses of the peaceful creation left behind mixed with a new world of choices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Hours</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/afterhours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/afterhours/</guid>
      <description>I grew up listening to a lot of different musical styles. Living about 60 miles north of New Orleans back then, some late Summer nights and weekends I would try to tune my old radio to those distant Jazz stations. After Hours is an attempt to create something smooth and jazz like. I used a Gretsch Streamliner for both guitar tracks, and a Fernandes bass. I hope you enjoy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Christmas Hymns</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/3christmashymns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/3christmashymns/</guid>
      <description>Recorded in 2017, this project includes three Christmas hymns. One is an instrumental.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1978</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/1978/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/1978/</guid>
      <description>A rock instrumental featuring a 1978 Ibanez Les Paul PF100! I picked up this guitar on the used rack at a local Nashville guitar shop. I fell in love with it&amp;rsquo;s playability and sound.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dawn of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/dawnofanewday/</guid>
      <description>Dawn of a New Day is a keyboard / synthesizer based instrumental work with cinematic overtones. Inspired by the thought that the future is still ahead, the past is behind! Seize the dawn of a new day&amp;hellip;
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>Simple piano and raspy vocals underpin a soulful ballad about keeping the faith and not giving up on tomorrow!
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfinished Business</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/unfinishedbusiness/</guid>
      <description>Released in September 2018, Unfinished Business was a labor of love featuring 7 original piano based works. Tracks that appeared to interest listeners were On Hold, Workin&#39; Toward Something, and Pillow Fight.
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Where Fast</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/nowherefast/</guid>
      <description>No Where Fast released in March 2018, arrived with 10 original songs! Some of the fan favorites are &amp;hellip;
Pretty Little Lies &amp;ndash; a cynical commentary of the times, Now I Do, a ballad about the blessings of small town life, and Road To Amarillo, a guitar grooving instrumental!
 Also find it here:
Spotify
YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Way from Home</title>
      <link>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waynecater.com/recordings/longwayfromhome/</guid>
      <description>Containing 12 original songs and recorded in 2017, Long Way from Home features a mix of songs ranging from warm ballads like Don&amp;rsquo;t Go Away to upbeat Goin&#39; Down This Road. Thought provoking lyrical tracks like Things to Think About remind one of what is important at the end of the day! There is an underlying feel to much of this recording that is Eagle&amp;rsquo;s like.
 Also find it here:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
